CONTACT ME AT

• Melbourne, Victoria

srisainee2310@gmail.com

littlebravesri.github.io

in linkedin.com/in/sri-saineethirumurugan/

github.com/littlebravesri

EDUCATION

Master of Data Science | RMIT University

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering | Anna University

SKILLS SUMMARY

•••• Python

••• SQL

• • • • Machine Learning

•••• Java

••• R

•••• Data Analysis

••• Data Visualization

•••• Azure

SRI SAINEE THIRUMURUGAN

DATA SCIENTIST

PERSONAL PROFILE

Master of Data Science graduate having well developed teamwork, communication and problem-solving skills broadened during academic experience. Possessing extensive knowledge in Python, SQL, Azure and OOPs through experience in projects. Confident about actively engaging in a dynamic and challenging environment to develop personal growth while contributing to the organization's success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data and Analytics Officer

Dementia Australia | August 2021 - September 2021 (Contract)

- Researched on integrity and consistency in all forms in the website.
- Reported tags and triggers functionality of the website in Google Tag manager and Google Analytics.
- Integrated MailChimp, Eventbrite, Google Analytics and Formstack into PowerBI and designed a dashboard to help improve marketing strategy.

Data Analyst Intern

Wings Cyberspcae International | April 2021 - July 2021

- Compared different web scraping tools to extract eBay product details including BeautifulSoup, Scrapy, ParseHub and Octoparse.
- Learnt Elasticsearch and how to upload data into Elasticsearch.
- Designed dashboards using Kibana, Tableau and PowerBI with extracted eBay product details.

Data Science and Analytics Intern

The Sparks Foundation | October 2020 - October 2020

- Performed Business Analysis by developing PowerBi dashboard
- Developed storyboard using Tableau to perform Time Series Analysis on COVID-19.
- Built interactive and animated visualizations to analyse the COVID data.
- Performed storytelling by interactive graphs enabling easy analysis.